**Free 2-Day Shipping on Thousands of Items!**

The World's Favorite Source Since 1997

        ----------------------------------------------------

        ----------------------------------------------------------------

        ----------------------------------------------------------

        ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
        
        --------------------------------------------------------------------

        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

        -------------------------------------------------------------------

        --------------------------------------------------------------------

        ------------------------------------------------------------------

    * Contact Information
        -------------------
        
        * Monday-Friday 9am-5pm ET
          
        * Product Inquiries [info@thegpsstore.com](mailto:info@thegpsstore.com)
          
        * Order Inquiries [sales@thegpsstore.com](mailto:sales@thegpsstore.com)

GPS Units - Accessories
-----------------------

--------------------------------------------

Privacy & Security
==================

Privacy Policy
--------------

The GPS Store, Inc. is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and to protect any personal information provided online, therefore we offer the following privacy policy.

**Basic confidentiality policy**  
It is our policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and email address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you supply is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information (such as to respond to a request or to process your order). You may be contacted via text or email to confirm your order.  
We do send occasional emails to our customers with promotions and/or special offers. You may opt out of these emails at any time.

For customers in California we comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act(CCPA) of 2018, Bill AB 375. California AB 375 can be found on the [State of California legislature website](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/billTextClient.xhtml?bill_id=201720180AB375). You can also find a detailed breakdown and answer to FAQ's regarding the CCPA by [clicking this link](https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa).

**No Release of information  
**Personal information will not be released to any third parties _except_ to further the purpose for which you provide the information (such as confirming an address for credit card processing). If further verification is required we may contact you via text or email. We do not provide your information to third parties for any other reason. We never sell your information to third parties.

**Statistics Tracking  
**While our website does track statistics about visits to our website such as daily number of visitors, most popular pages and referrals to our website, the statistics contain no personal information, and are used strictly internally to provide better service.

Secure Online Ordering
----------------------

We take security seriously as our website offers secure ordering for your protection. We frequently update the security of our site to follow the current “Best Practices”. Our Website uses TLS (Transport Layer Security), an encryption technology that works with Apple Safari, Google Chrome, Microsoft Internet Explorer and Mozilla Firefox browser so that only The GPS Store can read a buyer's personal information. As of January 2017 all pages on our site are secure with TLS. All account information submitted to us is safely isolated from unauthorized Internet access. Credit cards are not charged until the day the items are shipped.

Nevertheless, if you prefer, we also offer you the option of submitting your order by telephone, fax, or mail.

#### Store Links

#### Marine Electronics

#### Support

#### CONTACT

* **The GPS Store, Inc.**
* 6899 Beach Drive
* Ocean Isle Beach, NC 28469
* Questions ?
* Email [info@thegpsstore.com](mailto:info@thegpsstore.com)
* 910-575-9544

© 2024 The GPS Store, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
